

Software Engineer seeking roles in Software Development, Application Programming, System Programming, Agile Methodology, Requirement Gathering, Client Management, Technical Analysis, Project Management, Core Java, Java Script, Spring Boot, JIRA, Confluence, JUnit



Current Designation: Software Engineer Total Experience: 3 Year(s) 7 Month(s)

Current Company: Go Digit General Insurance Notice Period: Currently Serving Notice Period

Current Location: Pune Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Computers]

Pref. Location: Pune

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Married

Key Skills: software engineer, software development, application programming, client management, technical analysis,project management,core java,javascript,spring boot,jira,rest,SQL,MySQL,Oracle,JPA,JEE

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 22-Jan-21 Last Modified: 22-Jan-21

### Summary

3 years of experience in Java Development.

Designed and developed web applications in Core Java, Spring, JUnit and SQL with exposure to JSP, JSTL, JavaScript and basic AngularJS.

Well versed with the Agile methodology of Software Development life cycle and TDD approach.

Good understanding of OOPS concepts.

Worked in Activiti, Drools, Selenium and Fitnesse.

Good experience in client communication for requirement gathering, communication with onsite counterpart for technical clarification and functional requirements.

Highly dependable and enthusiastic team player dedicated to streamlining processes and efficiently resolving project issues. Good work ethics with good communication and interpersonal skills.

# Work Experience

Go Digit General Insurance as Software Engineer Jan 2019 to Jan 2019

Go Digit General Insurance as Software Engineer

Jan 2019 to Till Date

Go-digit General insurance is start up in general insurance which using ABS as product to sell insurance. ABS stand for Allianz Business System. Its Inventory management system which is used globally within Allianz group.

This "one-stop shop" approach allows business experts a singular interface for defining insurance products into their marketplace (Almost all over the world). ABS is built upon RCP Application and used internal development framework.

BNY Mellon as Application Developer Nov 2016 to Jan 2019

#### **Education**

#### UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computers) from Pune Institute Of Computer Technology, Pune in 2016

Other Qualifications/Certifications/Programs:

Diploma in Computer Engineering

#### IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
MICROSOFT WINDOWS			3 Year(s) 6 Month(s)
Core Java, J2EE, Drools, JUnit			3 Year(s) 6 Month(s)
SQL, JSP, JSTL, JavaScript, AngularJS			3 Year(s) 0 Month(s)
Spring MVC, Spring Boot, Spring REST			3 Year(s) 6 Month(s)
ABS Framework, Apache Tomcat, JBoss			2 Year(s) 2 Month(s)
Oracle10g, RCP, Activiti, Eclipse IDE			1 Year(s) 7 Month(s)
Selenium, Fitnesse, JIRA, Confluence			3 Year(s) 6 Month(s)
SVN, JIRA, Apache Maven			3 Year(s) 3 Month(s)
Jenkins			3 Year(s) 6 Month(s)

## **Languages Known**

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English	Proficient			
Hindi	Proficient			
Marathi	Proficient			

### **Affirmative Action**

Category: General Job Type: Permanent

Physically Challenged: No Employment Status: Full time

**Work Authorization**